

Profile

Full-stack developer with 8+ years of experience

• Top skills: Vue, React, Node

I have got 8+ years of experience as a full-stack developer.

Love to work with JS frameworks which are the most popular frameworks nowadays.

Worked in many remote teams and companies and completed many web projects using these techs.

I combine my present knowledge and extensive research into your business domain to create a modern professional website that will help you scale your business online by communicating your message to the audience and integrating systems like analytic, real-time customer support, tracking status, etc.

I am looking for a client who cares for quality work.

If this sounds like you, then you can pick me with the assurance of quality and best service.

Always provides professional coding structure, clean code.

Let's work together!

Employment History

Full stack developer at MC+A, Chicago

March 2021 — June 2021

Worked as a full stack developer.

Tech stack

- React
- GraphQL
- Elasticsearch
- Neo4i
- GRAND stack
- Jest & Enzyme

Built search website on private projects using Elasticsearch and Algolia.

Mainly worked with GraphQL + Node + React.

Front end developer at Redman Technologies Inc, EDMONTON, ALBERTA

January 2021 — June 2021

https://www.paranych.com/

https://www.canmorerealestate.com/

Tech stack

Details

46A WATTEN VIEW Singapore, 287177 Singapore

jinzhengyou0903@gmail.com

Date of birth Sep 3 1992

Links

Linkedin Github

Skills

Vue

React

Angular

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

TypeScript

Node.js

AWS services

Laravel

GraphQL

WebSocket

WebRTC

MySQL

SQL

MongoDB

Neo4i

Git

Jira

- Vue (SSR)
- Google Map
- Jest

Built CMS system using Vue.

Provide reusable and salable, mobile-responsive components.

Solved issues from server-side rendering.

Full stack developer at M6Connect, 1822 N 169TH PLAZA, OMAHA, NE 68118

October 2020 — March 2021

https://www.m6connect.com/

Tech stack

- Laravel/Firebase/AWS
- Vue/Vuetify
- WebRTC
- Jest

Mainly focused on the front end part but also worked on the back end part too.

Developed a project management system.

Full stack developer at SelfEmployed, Israel

February 2020 — February 2021

https://tradinglever.leverium.com/

https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/tradinglever-stock-analys/kepekocoibajpcejdpoccnlekokogogc

Tech stack

- Express
- SQLite
- AgGrid
- React
- Extension development

TradingLever allows you to load a stock list from any news article you are reading and, from there, you can analyze them.

Also developed extension for this project.

Full stack developer at KR Soft, Remote

February 2018 — January 2019

https://www.weroad.it/

http://petrolprices.com/

Tech stack

- Vue/Nuxt/Vuetify/ElementUI
- React/Next/Hook/Redux
- · Express/Laravel

Developed many web applications using JS frameworks.

Full stack developer at Upwork, Remote

October 2017 — February 2018

Languages

English

Korean

Hobbies

Swimming, table tennis, joking

https://borrowen.com/home

https://teachable.com/

Tech stack

- Angular/Vue/React
- Node/Express/Laravel

Worked as a freelancer in upwork.

Worked in many remote teams.

Web Developer at Tencent, Shenzhen, Guangdong, China

March 2014 — September 2017

Web Software Developer.

https://www.therugcompany.com/row/

https://www.keukenkiosk.nl/

https://www.neurosurgerycost.com/

- PHP, Laravel, CI
- React, Vue

Education

Master's degree, Beijing Institute of Technology

September 2012 — April 2014

Bachelor's degree, Incheon National University

September 2009 — April 2012

Courses

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Microsoft Professional Program in Front-End Web Development

Certified Internet Webmaster Web Developer (CIW)